The past never stays buried.
The Unholy Trinity is a western, adventure, crime film directed by Richard Gray.
Set against the turbulent backdrop of 1870s Montana, in the moments before the execution of Isaac Broadway, he gives his
estranged son, Henry, an impossible task: murder the man who framed him for a crime he didn’t commit.
Intent on fulfilling his promise, Henry travels to the remote town of Trinity, where an unexpected turn of events traps him in town
and leaves him caught between Gabriel Dove, the town’s upstanding new sheriff, and a mysterious figure named St.
Christopher.
Gabriel Dove, played by Pierce Brosnan.
St. Christopher, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
Henry Broadway, played by Brandon Lessard.
Sarah Dove, played by Veronica Ferres.
Gideon, played by Gianni Capaldi.
Running Cub, played by Q'orianka Kilcher.
The Unholy Trinity is a 2024 American Western action film written by Lee Zachariah,
directed by Richard Gray, and starring Pierce Brosnan, Samuel L.
Jackson, and Brandon Lessard, and follows a young man who travels to the
titular town of Montana to avenge his father's death.
It received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of montana, false accusations,
19th century, imminent execution, 1870s.